http://www.plumpton.ac.uk/cookies-privacy-policy/

See our live apprenticeship vacancies by clicking here
MenuSite searchSearch keyword(s): SearchHomeCoursesCourse Types14-16 Courses16+ CoursesUniversity CoursesPart Time CoursesApprenticeshipsApprenticeship ProgrammesApprenticeship VacanciesApprenticeship Talent BankBespoke CoursesDepartmentsAdventure Education & SportAgricultureAnimal ManagementBlacksmithing & MetalworkEnvironmental Studies & ConservationEquine ManagementFisheries & Aquatic ScienceFloristryFood SkillsForest SchoolForestry & ArboricultureFoundation LearningGame & Wildlife ManagementHorticultureLand Based EngineeringMotor VehicleSchool Programmes & VisitsPrimary Schools Events CalendarSecondary Schools Events CalendarVeterinary Nursing & Dog GroomingWine DivisionWine Degree CoursesWine ApprenticeshipsWine Part-Time CoursesMeet the Wine DivisionWine Research & PodcastsWine Division StudentsPlumpton Estate WinesContact Wine DivisionStudent InfoImportant information for StudentsBeing on CampusYour Timetable and LessonsResidency InformationIT Access for StudyStudent InductionStudent Covid Secure DeclarationStudent SafetyStudent Enrolment14-16 Student Welcome InformationCourse Equipment ListImportant Questions AnsweredVirtual 2020 Awards CeremonyStudent Absence ReportAdditional Learning SupportCareersCareer VacanciesCollege AccommodationFood & DietFunding & Loans16+ FinanceCollege Bursary ApplicationHigher Education FinanceHow to ApplyOnline PaymentsOur FacilitiesShopSportsFishingEstateOur campusesBwlch MwlchanFlimwellStanmer CampusLibraryResearchPlumpton Online (VLE)Student ActivitiesStudent SupportStudent HealthStudent CounsellingStudent WellbeingStudent UnionTerm TimesTravelWho We AreAlumniGovernance & PoliciesFreedom of InformationHistoryPlumpton Roman VillaMessage from the PrincipalOur Strategic PlanOur ValuesPlumpton Charitable FoundationThe Friends of Plumpton CollegeResultsBusiness ServicesApprenticeships For EmployersApprenticeship Live VacanciesApprenticeship Recruitment SupportDigital Apprenticeship ServiceEmployer VacanciesBespoke Courses for EmployersLegislative Short CoursesCommunity Information HubConferencing and Event FacilitiesOur VenueMeetings and ConferencesEaster and Summer BookingsBespoke EventsNews & UpdatesCOVID-19 UpdatesNewsCalendar of EventsUpcoming EventsPast EventsSportsPlumpton College Job VacanciesVLEOnline PaymentsSchools PortalShopContact us HomeCookies & Privacy PolicyCookies & Privacy Policy
This privacy notice tells you what to expect when Plumpton College collects personal information.  It covers why we collect personal information, how we use it and how we keep it secure. It applies to information we collect about: Visitors to our website People who register to attend, or attend, one of the College Information Events run by Plumpton College People who enquire about courses at Plumpton College People who apply and enrol for courses at Plumpton College People who phone the main college reception We may change this policy from time to time, so please check this page occasionally to ensure you're still happy with the policy. By using the website, you're agreeing to the terms within this policy. We are committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors to our website and do not disclose personal data of our users to third-parties. Information that we collect about you is held securely and is processed along clear guidelines that do not affect your data protection rights. How do we collect information from you? Web analytics When someone visits our website we use web analytics to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. Site search Search terms used on our website are collected and processed anonymously to help improve our website and search functionality. No user-specific data is collected by the College. College Information Event registrations – Course Enquiries When registering for events or making course enquiries we will ask you to complete some basic information regarding your name, contact details, subject area(s) you are interested in studying and the level of study (full-time, undergraduate, apprenticeships or part-time).  You may also be asked about your current situation, including school/college currently attending and likely year of entry.  This data is collected to ensure we can provide you with the information that you may need to study with us, and improve the advice that we provide you with, as well as understand the geographic reach that we have as an educational provider.  At the time of requesting the information your consent to process this data will be sought. This data will be held for a maximum of three years, or until the expected year of entry to the College (as determined by the information submitted and your date of birth) has passed. Course applications and enrolments The personal information you provide when applying for or enrolling onto a course is passed to the relevant government departments who fund Plumpton College in order to allow them to meet their statutory responsibilities and to create and maintain the unique learner number (ULN) and individual learning record (ILR). We will not collect any personal data from you we do not need in order to provide the best possible learning experience to you. The information you provide may also be used to inform college demographic, wellbeing, research and performance data – this is done on an anonymised basis to better inform future college strategy Phone calls To maintain customer service standards, and assist in staff training, we may record and monitor incoming telephone calls. The information you supply will enable us to assist you with your enquiry and provide you with the best possible service. It could also enable us to contact you, where necessary, to follow up any questions you may have. Social media If you participate in any discussion on our social media platforms, you may provide us with information such as your name and address, email or phone number. What we do with your data Plumpton College will be the ‘Data Controller’ of the personal data you provide to us. All personal data is processed by relevant Plumpton College staff.  This data is located and stored on servers managed and overseen by system managers who act as data processors and are compliant with the provisions of the GDPR. No third parties have access to your personal data unless the law or you allows them to do so. Hard copies of your personal data may be kept, and these are retained in lockable storage units. We have a Data Protection policy in place to oversee the effective and secure processing of your personal data. CONTACT PREFERENCES FOR STUDENTS If you are one of our current students your success is of paramount importance to us. To this end we reserve the right to contact you regarding your enrolment, course progression and for any other matter that we feel is ultimately related to your course achievement and student enrichment. We will contact you based upon the contact details that we hold for you. We will not contact you about other courses, college products and events without your consent but we do recognise that these may be of interest to you. If you’d like us to keep you up to date about wider college matters and other course opportunities you can indicate your preference when you enrol. Marketing and Research We would like to send you information about our range of courses, and other services that we offer, which we feel may be of interest to you. You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing and research purposes and as such even if you have previously given consent to receive promotional information from us you may opt out at a later date. If you no longer wish to be contacted for such purposes please email us at enquiries@plumpton.ac.uk. We will not share your information for marketing purposes with third-party organisations. Access to your information and correction You have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, please email us.  We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or remove information you think is inaccurate. Cookies a. Cookies may be used by the Website to allow us to recognise you and your preferred settings e.g. to store your ID and password for future sessions. This saves you from re-entering information on return visits to the Website. You have the option not to use this feature, in which event no cookies will be retained on your computer. b. If the site has a secure log-in for our registered users, it may use a temporary ’session cookie’ in order to perform the secure login to our website. This cookie contains no personal information, just a long random number, and is deleted from your web browser when you exit the Website. c. Temporary cookies are used in the transactional part of the Website to authenticate you as an authorised user after you have logged in. d. Your browser may be capable of being programmed to reject cookies, or to warn you before downloading cookies, and information regarding this may be found in your browser’s ‘help’ facility. For an explanation of cookies see the All About Cookies website. If you have any questions regarding the use of cookies please contact us. Below is a table of all cookies on this website – their name, type and purpose: Cookie TypeCookie Name Cookie PurposeSession & TYPO3 Content Management Cookiesession & fe_typo_userWe use session cookies to record an individual users preferences that the user has specified, so that each time the user returns their preferences remain. Commonly this would be language settings, shopping carts, anything where you have indicated a preference. Where forms are used on the site, we hold the information in a session cookie so that we can improve the user experience on the site. Should a user, for example, forget to fill in parts of a form when submitting a form, we can auto-fill the values for those fields that have been filled in, thereby reducing the amount of fields a user needs to amend. This information is stored only in your browser and is destroyed once your browser is closed.Google Analytics__utmz __utmc __utmb __utmaThese cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site for you. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. We use third party companies as suppliers for some of our functions. Their use of the data is controlled by our contract with them and they are only allowed to use the data strictly for the purpose we have stated e.g. the data is not used in connection with data from other companies and we are not tracking user behavior outside our own sites.
Other websites Our website may contain links to third-party websites and partner sites. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the collation of any personal information by third parties whose privacy policy is different to ours. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit. Changes to our privacy policy We keep our privacy notice under regular review and we will place any updates on this webpage. This policy was last updated on 23rd May 2018. How to contact us Please contact us if you have any questions about this privacy policy, or information we hold about you: by email – enquiries@plumpton.ac.uk by writing to Plumpton College, Ditchling Road, Lewes, East Sussex, BN7 3AE
Terms & ConditionsCookies & Privacy PolicyAccessibility StatementSitemapSearch
Terms & ConditionsCookies & Privacy PolicyAccessibility StatementSitemapSearchFacebookInstagramLinkedInTwitter
© 2020 Plumpton CollegeWeb design agency - Liquid Light
You are currently offline. Some pages or content may fail to load.
